Liza was supposed to surrender.
Something bad must have
happened to her.
I know where she might be.
That's the only place I know.
They don't trust me that much.
I've been through
a lot with this person.
I want to be the one
to catch him myself.
Where will you hold the meeting?
I have a plan.
Are you attending tomorrow?
Yes, where will this be held?
At the old quarry.
Is Jin Ho still asleep?
Did Oppa escape again?
I think he's looking for Liza.
The Korean escaped from me.
He even took my gun.
I'm coming for you, Liza.
Don't worry, Liza.
I won't prolong your suffering.
Follow that car.
Where are we taking Liza?
Anywhere we pass
where there are no people.
Let's find Jin Ho!
We're following
a subject right now.
- Possible target.
- That's Dad.
Block them!
Who are they following?
[OBB]
- Bolagos Police!
- What is it, Sir?
- Who are you with?
- I'm alone, Sir.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Window.
There it is.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sorry, we're just looking
for someone.
It's okay, Sir.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where are you, Berdugo?
[REVVING]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
That's beautiful, Berdugo.
It's worth every peso
I spent on it.
I'll christen this now.
Stop the car.
Go on, let Liza out.
Go on, let her out.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Make sure no one sees you.
Okay, Boss.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUFFLED PLEADING]
Goodbye, Liza.
[GUN FIRES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
That's for you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you sure, Berdugo?
You are the only one loyal
to me and our group.
That's your reward.
Thank you.
Everything you ask me to do,
I'll do.
I know.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's that on the side
of the road?
Stop the car.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
It's Liza!
X-Alpha unit, come in.
Yes, Cruz?
Major, positive.
We found Liza here.
She was salvaged.
It was done in the grassland.
Okay, we're on our way!
[BRAZEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
Liza!
Liza, Liza...
Liza...
Sir, let's take her
to the hospital!
No.
Please tell Jin Ho...
I'm sorry.
No, you'll tell him yourself.
We'll take you to the hospital.
Liza, where are your companions?
Where is Berdugo?
Quarry.
Quarry?
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Thank you.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you, everyone!
Thank you! You're all...
You're all too kind.
Right, Hon?
They're not only kind
but, also very generous.
That's true.
You know, with all your help,
the Hope Circle Foundation
will be able to build
the Angel Sanctuary.
And we're doing all this
for the children, our future.
So, on behalf of the whole
foundation and the children,
we would like to thank
all of you so much.
Thank you.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
Thank you so much.
[CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPPING]
Picture, picture!
[AMBULANCE SIREN WAILING]
Looks like they're eliminating
each other.
Maybe they're just eliminating
those who turned against them.
Because isn't that what they
wanted to do to Jin Ho?
Dad, do you have any news about
Jin Ho's whereabouts?
Maybe he already left
the country.
What's important is that I get
to the quarry Liza mentioned.
Maybe Berdugo is there.
We'll come with you, Major.
No.
Just go home.
There are guards there too.
Can I count on you?
Cruz...
give them their phones.
If there's a problem,
just call me.
I have a strong feeling
Jin Ho won't leave the country.
Where could our friend be now?
Go ahead, you can leave now.
Take care, Dad.
You take care too.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Cruz, this day won't end
without us getting Berdugo.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[REVVING]
[HEAVY MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry, Liza.
[REVVING]
[GUN FIRES]
[HEAVY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[REVVING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Liza...
Look at me, Liza.
No...
no, Liza!
[SHOUTS]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[POLICE SIREN WAILING
IN DISTANCE]
[MOTORCYCLE REVVING]
Sir, here's the CCTV footage.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Impressive, huh.
- What kind of gun is that?
These syndicates
are something else.
Even their guns are customized.
Who could be handling
those guns?
Only one person comes to mind.
Send a copy of that to
the Chief.
Also find out who the vehicle
is registered to,
and call for additional backup.
Captain, thank you very much.
All right, Sir.
We'll go ahead.
Men, let's move!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[REVVING]
Andrew, where are you going?
Major said we should stay at the
house for the meantime.
Andrew, stay here, please.
Okay.
- [PHONE RINGING]
- Oh, answer it.
Put it on speaker, speaker.
Hello?
Hello, Joey?
Hey, Oppa, why did you
escape again?
You just created trouble.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho, where are you?
Oh, wait a minute.
You're asking him
too many questions right away.
Jin Ho, we're worried about you.
We're at our house now.
Just come here.
I know.
And I'm sorry to leave you all
like this.
Jin Ho, listen to me.
Jin Ho, you're smart enough
to understand
that you're only making
your situation worse.
Come here.
We, your friends,
can still help you fix this.
Okay?
Please, Jin Ho.
I am so thankful to all of you,
for being my friends.
Especially you, Joey.
But I can't go there right now.
Because I have to avenge Liza.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN COCKS]
You will have your revenge,
Liza.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sometimes, I get annoyed
at Jin Ho too.
But like you said,
he is our friend.
Let's go, let's find him.
Congrats to all of us.
Ah, I'm so excited, really.
You're so lucky, Mr. Limjoco.
Your wife is really so kind.
I know. I married a saint.
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
That's why I hope she'll be the
key for me to enter heaven.
Wow.
Oh, my husband,
he way he talks,
it's as if he's a bad person.
You really are something else.
[PHONE CHIMES]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hon, excuse me.
- Yes?
I just need to check something.
Ah, okay.
Excuse.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I got you, Berdugo.
Are you sure you want to do
this, Jin Ho?
You're making a big mistake.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You must have heard the news
of your beloved Liza.
I saw you with my own eyes.
You killed her.
And now...
it is your time to die!
What's the meaning of this?
Aren't you Major Delgado,
the husband of Clarissa?
Someone told us
that the group
we're looking for is here
along with their leader.
What?
These are decent
and kind people here.
They are the sponsors
of my foundation.
Ma'am, we're sorry.
We're just doing our job.
And besides, it's hard
to trust so easily.
Fine.
Search the area!
Yes, Sir!
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is for Liza.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Then do it or else...
I'm going to kill you next!
[GUN FIRING]
- [CROWD CLAMORING]
- Sir...
[GUN FIRING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
It sounded like the shots
came from there!
Let's track it!
You stay here!
[GUN FIRING]
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
[GROANS]
[GUN FIRING]
[BRAZEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
Jin Ho!
Berdugo!
Good thing I found you!
We need to leave!
Mr. Stuart didn't come!
You scared me!
Where's Berdugo?
But Joey, we need to leave now.
Berdugo?
He's here?
Yes.
Where?
Let's go!
Berdugo!
[GUN FIRING]
We need to get him out of here
before Berdugo finishes him!
- Come on! Let's go, let's go!
- Let's go!
How about Berdugo?
- He killed Liza!
Dad will deal with him!
Let's go!
[GUN FIRING]
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
- Let's go!
[BRAZEN MUSIC CONTINUES]
Berdugo, surrender now!
[GUN FIRING]
Berdugo!
I'm out of bullets, Berdugo.
I'll give you ten seconds!
You still have a chance to live!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We have no choice.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Any moment now...
Finally, you can live
peacefully now.
That's right.
Now, Mom and I can truly say
our lives are back to normal.
We no longer need to watch
our back, Mom,
afraid that someone
has bad intentions toward us,
right?
That's right.
And at last,
we can breathe freely.
Thank God.
Good morning, everybody.
At long last, we got him.
Berdugo has finally been caught.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, there's Miguel.
Your father!
Thanks to the tireless efforts
of our police
led by Major Miguel Delgado.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
- [WHOOPING]
- That's my father!
Turn on the TV.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay.
Thank you.
Even the Department
of Drug Enforcement
was part of the search
for Berdugo
And today...
he was captured.
Now...
let's allow Major Delgado
to tell us
how Berdugo was caught.
Major Delgado.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
Good day.
It was difficult, exhausting,
and I even had to risk my life
to capture Berdugo.
But even though he was slick,
we tracked him down at a quarry
with his associates.
Berdugo's group
is the biggest drug dealer
in the Visayas.
So where is Berdugo now?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
He's right there.
Now, we will see the face...
behind the name Berdugo.
Cruz.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
So that's Berdugo.
That man right there.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
I want to get my revenge.
He may not be dead,
but he's been caught.
This is the one
I fought with before,
and Tomas knows him too.
To be honest, my business with
Matias is fine
since his food business
is thriving.
But you told me before
your business was textiles.
It feels like
I found him too easily.
I have a hunch,
which I can't explain.
Nice to meet the daughter
of the bravest man I know.
I think I've heard
his voice before.
I'm right in front of you,
and you still can't do anything.
Do you think I'd stop?
Follow your gut, my son.
Everything is not
what it seems to be.
What do you mean?